Nice work out there, Ichiji, Niji.
أحسنتما عملًا يا إيتشيجي ونيجي
The war-torn Broc Coli is another victim of the fall of the Doflamingo regime, you could say.
اندلعت الحرب في بروكلي كنتيجة أخرى لسقوط نظام دوفلامينغو
Their army could no longer acquire weapons from Doflamingo, so they turned to us for help.
لم يعد جيشهم قادرًا على استيراد الأسلحة من دوفلامينغو، فطلبوا منا المساعدة
They gave up on the idea of merely suppressing their rivals...
توقفوا عن التفكير بمجرد دحر خصومهم
It's a good example of how halfhearted kindness only leads to more bloodshed in the end.
ذلك مثالٌ على العواقب الوخيمة للأفعال الطيبة
Who cares about the reason why?
لا تهم الأسباب
We just make it so whoever pays us gets to win, and that's it.
كل ما في الأمر أننا نساعد من يدفع لنا
If we had crushed both sides, we could've earned even more money.
يمكننا ربح مال أكثر إن سحقنا كِلا الطرفين
That's what pirates would do.
ذلك يجعلنا مماثلين للقراصنة
We're still a member nation of the World Government.
نحن ما نزال دولة عضوة في حكومة العالم
Speaking of which, Father, the Reverie will take place soon.
بالمناسبة يا أبي، سيُعقد الليفيلي قريبًا
Yes.
أجل
However, they'll likely strip us of our right to attend the Reverie starting from this one.
ولكن من المرجح أنهم سيجردوننا من حق المشاركة في الليفيلي بدءًا من هذه المرة
All of you, be prepared for it!
حضّروا أنفسكم لذلك
The power that we'll get in exchange is tremendous!
فالقوة التي سنتلقاها في المقابل هائلة
Germa will change!
الجيرما ستتغير
It's rare for anything to bring so much pleasure to Father.
نادرًا ما تحدث أشياء تثير سعادة أبي
I can't believe you came in handy, after all.
لم أتوقع أنك صرتَ ذا فائدة
Sanji!
يا سانجي
We were surprised on the day that you disappeared.
كنا متفاجئين يوم اختفائك
Truly.
جديًّا
We used to talk about you from time to time.
نحن إخوتك كنا نتحدث عنك بين حينٍ وآخر
We wondered where the funniest place for you to die would be, and how it might happen.
تساءلنا عن أي طريقة ممتعة هلكت بها يا تُرى
You still have food on your plate, Niji. Eat all of it.
تركتَ بعضًا من طعامك يا نيجي، تناول كل شيء
This? I'll just leave it. I'm not hungry.
هذا؟ سأتركه، لا أريد تناوله
I ate tons of chocolate earlier, and this sauce that's poured on it looks nasty.
تناولت الكثير من الشوكولاتة قبل قليل وهذه الصلصة المسكوبة على الطعام لا تبدو جيدة
It's all sticky and gross.
إنها لزجة ومقززة
I'm throwing this away.
سأرميه في القمامة
Eat it!
تناوله
You don't know how valuable food is or how much work goes into cooking, you dumb prince!
أنت لا تعرف قيمة الطعام أو المجهود المبذول في إعداده أيها الأمير الأحمق
Dumb?!
أحمق؟
You're a weakling, Sanji!
أنت لست سوى سانجي الضعيف
Don't you dare insult me, much less give me orders!
لا يحق لك إهانتي أو توجيه أوامرٍ لي
Call the head chef! Where are you, Cosette?!
أحضروا رئيسة الطهاة، أين هي كوزيت؟
Because you served this disgusting stuff, my brother has offended me!
بسبب تقديمك لهذا الطعام المقزز قام أخي الأصغر بإهانتي
Yes, sir! I'm sorry!
حاضرة، أقدم خالص اعتذاري
I shouldn't serve anything unpalatable to you...
لا يجدر بي تقديم شيء لا يروق لك يا نيجي-ساما
Okay.
حسنًا
Stay right there, Cosette.
لا تتحركي يا كوزيت
You bastard... How low will you sink?!
أيها اللعين، إلى أي مدى تصل حقارتك؟
Are you trying to leave a scar on a lady's face?!
أتحاول إحداث ندبة دائمة بوجه سيدة؟
What did you say? A lady?
ماذا؟ أقلت سيدة؟
Why are you defending a mere kitchen maid?!
لماذا تدافع عن طاهية من الخدم الحثالة؟
What a gentleman.
يا للشهامة
Now the food's on the floor.
سقط الطعام على الأرض
This is aligot. It's a mixture of potatoes and cheese.
هذا الطبق يسمى أليغو ويُصنع من الجبن المخلوط بالبطاطس
Your Highness, I'll clean it!
سانجي-ساما، سأنظفه أنا
Potatoes strengthen the immune system and stabilize blood pressure.
البطاطس تزيد قوة مناعتك وتساعد على استقرار ضغط الدم
They're very nutritious.
هي مغذية للغاية
And maybe because you guys are so special,
ولأنكم من ذوي الأهمية، فإنّ قطعة اللحم المطهوة ببطء هذه تمّ انتقاؤها بعناية كذلك
It's a very elaborate dish to make for breakfast.
إنه طبق فاخر بالنسبة لكونه إفطارًا
Oh, please don't, Your Highness!
لا تفعل يا سانجي-ساما
Royalty mustn't eat food off the floor!
لا يجدر بشخص من العائلة الملكية أن يتناول طعامًا من الأرض
Hey, are you out of your mind?! That's disgusting!
هل جننت أيها اللعين؟ هذا مقزز
It's perfectly flavored, too.
والنكهة مثالية كذلك
The spirit of the poor has taken root in you!
لقد تأصلت فيك روح الفقراء
Stop doing such a disgraceful thing!
كفّ عن هذه الأفعال المخزية
Don't, Niji! He hasn't been married yet!
توقف يا نيجي، فالزفاف وشيك
Thank you, sir.
شكرًا جزيلًا
You only bring shame to the Vinsmokes.
لست سوى عارٌ على عائلة فينسموك
What's shameful to me is being part of this family!
ما يجلب لي العار هو كوني جزءًا من هذه العائلة
What?!
ماذا؟
An idiot who has no respect for food. A man who beats a woman!
أحمق لا يحترم الطعام، ورجل يضرب امرأة
The arrogance of royalty that compels you to see your servants as less than human!
غطرسة الملوك تدفعكم لمعاملة خدمكم وكأنهم أقل منزلة من البشر
Everything about you guys goes against what I stand for!
كل أفعالكم تناقض مبادئي
What you're saying is the kind of nonsense all those losers spout, Sanji.
أنت تتفوه بكلام الفاشلين يا سانجي
I've never understood the way you see things.
لم أفهم قط ما كنت تقوله منذ كنا صغارًا
Royalty operates by its own set of rules!
يتصرف الملوك كما يطيب لهم
You're the unreasonable one!
أنت من يتعامل بأسلوب غير منطقي
He's right. You're more wrong than ever.
بالفعل، فأنت مخطئ
Is it because of the bad influence from this man, Sanji?
هل السبب في ذلك هو تأثير هذا الرجل يا سانجي؟
Big Mom's ability to collect information is greater than people think.
قدرة بيغ مام على جمع المعلومات تفوق الظن
So you were working at his restaurant until two years ago.
كنت تعمل بهذا المطعم حتى العامين الماضيين
We've already zeroed in on its location, too.
حددنا موقعه كذلك
Seems like this picture was taken recently.
...يبدو أن هذه الصورة قد أُلتُقِطت حديثًا
The sea restaurant, Baratie !
في مطعم البحر باراتي
What's wrong? You're turning pale.
ما الأمر؟ أصبح وجهك شاحبًا
Where did your spirit from earlier go, Sanji?
أين اختفت عزيمتك السابقة يا سانجي؟
Say something. Huh? Hey!
...قل شيئًا، هيا
What are those?
ما هذه؟
These are bracelets to prevent him from escaping-bon.
إنها أساور لمنعه من الهروب-بون
Seems like both the Straw Hats and Sanji himself are
يبدو أنّ طاقم قبعة القش وحتى سانجي سيعارضون هذا الزواج-بون
I'll lend you these bracelets and tell you his weak point just in case-soir.
تحسُّبًا لذلك، سأعيرك هذه الأساور وأخبرك بنقطة ضعفه-سوار
His weak point?
نقطة ضعفه؟
Well, only in the worst-case scenario where you refuse to comply
في أسوأ الأحوال، إن فقدنا القدرة على التحكم بك
will I stoop to asking you if you want us to chop his head off.
سأستعرض صورته تهديدًا لأذكرك بمقدرتنا على جز عنق ذلك الرجل
Don't do anything stupid. You know what we're capable of.
لا ترتكب أية حماقات، فأنت تعرف مدى قدرتنا
Don't ever resist.
إياك والمقاومة
Give up on your friends and accept your marriage to Pudding.
تخلّ عن أصدقائك واقبل هذا الزواج من بودينغ
Then, everything will wrap up neatly.
وسيكون كل شيء على ما يرام
What happened to your leg?
ما الذي أصاب ساقك تلك؟
Why?!
لماذا؟
I can't think of any reason for you to be kind to me!
لا أجد سببًا يدفعك لمعاملتي بطيبة
Why...? Why did you?!
لماذا؟ لماذا؟
Because you... have the same dream as me.
لأنك تملك نفس حلمي
The All Blue...
الأزرق الكامل؟
This is awesome, you damn geezer! Is this the sea restaurant?
مدهش أيها العجوز اللعين أهذا هو مطعم البحر؟
We're gonna be busy!
سيتوافد علينا الزبائن من كل حدبٍ وصوب
We'll be fine 'cause I'm here!
لا بأس، فأنا هنا
Hey, little eggplant!
أيها القزم
You're too slow, little eggplant!
أنت بطيء أيها القزم
I'm not, you damn geezer!
لستُ بطيئًا أيها العجوز اللعين
Fooling around with a woman again, little eggplant!
امرأة أخرى أيها القزم؟
Little eggplant!
أيها القزم
Sanji!
سانجي
Don't catch a cold.
لا تُصب بالبرد
Owner Zeff!!
أيها المالك زيف
Thank you for all the damn things you've done for me over all these years!
شكرًا على ما قدمته لي من أشياء لعينة طيلة السنوات الماضية
I'll never forget your kindness... for the rest of my life!
لن أنسى معاملتك الطيبة ما حييت
Let's have a peaceful wedding tomorrow.
فلنجعل زفاف الغد خاليًا من المشاكل
We'll have lunch with Big Mom and Pudding today.
سنتناول الغداء مع بيغ مام وبودينغ اليوم
Prepare to leave for her castle.
جهّز نفسك لزيارة القصر
Okay, Sanji?
أفهمت يا سانجي؟
Damn Straw Hat... Where did he go?
أين ذهب قبعة القش ذاك؟
Search for him.
اعثروا عليه
Ten minutes... is long...
الدقائق العشر طويلة جدًّا
I can't even use haki.
لا يمكنني حتى استخدام الهاكي
Is somebody there?
هل من أحد هناك؟
Somebody, help! Call a doctor!
فليساعدنا أحدكم، اتصلوا بالطبيب
Hey, stay with me!
تماسكي
Damn! They waited until I wasn't around!
سحقًا، لقد أستغلّوا عدم تواجدي بالجوار
What did she do to deserve this?!
ما الذي اقترفته لتستحق كل هذا؟
They beat a woman unconscious...
ضربوا امرأة حتى أفقدوها الوعي
I've never met such scum!
لم يسبق لي مقابلة حثالة كهؤلاء
It's your fault, Sanji.
أنت السبب يا سانجي
Yonji!
يونجي
You gave a woman of low birth a taste of self-confidence.
منحت هذه المرأة مكانًا أعلى مما تنتمي
What do you mean by that, you bastard?!
ماذا تعني بكلامك أيها اللعين؟
Do you want to see Niji? Obviously, he's the one who did it.
أتريد مقابلة نيجي؟ فهو من فعل هذا بالطبع
Follow me. I'll take you to him.
اتبعني، سأصحبك إليه
You're gonna be fine. Don't worry.
لا بأس، لا تقلقي
What's wrong? Are you coming?
ما الأمر؟ ألن تأتي؟
Yeah, I'm more than happy to!
بلى، هذا ما أريده فعلًا
This is...
...هذا المكان
You were curious, weren't you?
ألم يراودك الفضول؟
We were never allowed in here as kids.
لم يكن مسموحًا لنا الدخول هنا عندما كنا أطفالًا
54 Type MBs. 30 Type MSTs.
MBs نحتاج لتعويض 54 من نوع MH و21 من نوع ،MST و30 من نوع
Got it.
عُلِم
What are they?!
من يكون هؤلاء؟
Do you want to know what they are?
هل تتساءل عن هويتهم؟
Germa 66 is feared around the world.
الرعب من جيرما 66 يجتاح العالم
And these are its soldiers!
وهؤلاء جنودها
Minister Cracker!
كراكر-ساما
Cracker?! Is that him?!
كراكر؟ أذلك هو؟
What's wrong, Kingbaum?
ما الخطب يا كينغبوم؟
Why are you taking Straw Hat's side?
لماذا تتحالف مع طاقم قبعة القش؟
There is a good reason for it...
ثمة سبب لهذا
No excuse.
لا أريد أعذارًا
I'm gonna kill you all!
سأقتلكم جميعًا
What's with him?
ما خطبه؟
Woman, I'm Sweet Commander Cracker.
أيتها المرأة، أنا قائد الحلوى كراكر
Don't touch...
...رفيقتي
my friend!
لا تمسّها بسوء
Straw Hat!
قبعة القش
The soldiers of Germa 66?!
...جيرما 66 أهؤلاء جنودها؟
Why are they in water?
لِمَ هم في الماء؟
It's a bio-culture liquid.
إنه سائل التكنولوجيا الحيوية
They all have the same face... Are they actually alive?
جميعهم لهم الوجه ذاته هل هم على قيد الحياة؟
Sanji, human beings...
...سانجي، إن البشر
can be built!
قابلون للصنع
Germa has been a kingdom of science for generations.
لطالما كانت جيرما مملكة العلم على مرّ الأجيال
Believe it or not, our father is a brilliant scientist.
رغم ما يبدو، فقد كان والدنا شهيرًا بكونه عالمًا ماهرًا
Before we were born,
قبل أن نولد
he was part of a lawless research team in a foreign territory
كان عضوًا في فريق بحثي أجنبي خارج عن القانون
where he was studying and developing weapons with the great Dr. Vegapunk.
مع العالم الشهير فيغابانك، حيث كانا يعملان على تصنيع الأسلحة
He was with Vegapunk?!
هو وفيغابانك؟
Yes, when he was younger.
في أيام شبابهما
What Vegapunk discovered at that time was the presence of
ما حققه فيغابانك في ذلك الحين كان اكتشاف العناصر المحددة لتكوين السلالات في الكائنات الحية
It was just one step away from usurping God's place.
...لقد قاب قوسين أو أدنى من عالم الألوهية، لأن ما فعله كان أشبه
In essence, he found the blueprints of life.
باكتشاف المخططات التي خُلقت عن طريقها الحياة
The World Government saw it as dangerous and arrested Vegapunk.
اعتبرت حكومة العالم ذلك الاكتشاف خطرًا وقاموا بالقبض على فيغابانك
The research team was disbanded. Or rather, it was absorbed by the government.
تمّ حل الفريق البحثي، وأقصد بهذا أنّ الحكومة في الواقع قد أغرتهم بالانضمام لصفوفها بالمال
However, our father escaped the government's reach
ولكن والدنا تمكن من الهرب من قبضة الحكومة، وأكمل بحوثه هنا في جيرما
The research into replicating and augmenting life itself.
بحوثه المتعلقة بنسخ وتعديل الحياة
Thus leading to the birth of this secret facility!
ثم بُنيت هذه المنشأة الواقعة تحت سطح الأرض
They're all clones of just a few talented soldiers!
جميعهم نسخ من مجرد بضعة جنود موهوبين
They're clone soldiers!
«واسمهم «الجنود المستنسخون
Clone?!
مستنسخون؟
Of course, none of them are aware of that.
هم لا يعرفون هذه الحقيقة بالطبع
You see, Sanji?
أتعرف يا سانجي؟
Many countries are afraid of our army, but at the same time, they wish to have it.
العديد من الدول تخشى جيشنا ولكنها تتمنى حيازته في الوقت ذاته
It only makes sense; they are mighty and subservient.
وذلك منطقي، فهم أقوياء ومطيعون
They're programmed not to fear death and not to turn on their masters.
تمت برمجتهم بحيث لا يخشون الموت ولا يخونون أسيادهم
When they die, we can just replace them.
ويمكننا تعويضهم ببساطة عندما يموتون
It takes five years to create a 20-year-old soldier.
نحتاج إلى خمسة أعوام لصنع جندي بعمر 20 عامًا
This is the depot where we keep a stock of the soldiers.
هذا مستودع الجنود
Look. It only takes five years to create them,
انظر، إنشاؤهم يحتاج خمسة أعوام فقط
but they look like they've been around for two decades.
ولكنهم يبدون بعمر 20 عامًا
Stop it! That's enough!
توقف، هذا يكفي
I'm going to be sick.
أصبتني بالغثيان
Sanji.
سانجي
When we heard that you became a pirate,
:عندما سمعتُ بأنك أصبحت قرصانًا، قلت لنفسي «ربما كبر ذلك الفاشل وأصبح شخصًا أفضل»
But you ended up just as disappointing as ever.
ولكنك مخيب للآمال كالعادة
Niji!
نيجي
You sick bastard...
...أيها الوغد
What are you doing over there?
ماذا تفعلين في مكان كهذا؟
You kitchen maid.
أيتها الطاهية الحثالة
Um...
...المعذرة
What did Cosette-chan do...
...كوزيت-تشان
to deserve that?!
ماذا فعلت بحقها؟
What you did was a high crime! I'll teach you a lesson!
ما اقترفته كان جريمة نكراء، سأجعلك تدفع الثمن
Wait, Sanji! Don't forget that we're holding a hostage in the East Blue!
مهلًا يا سانجي، لا تنسَ أنّ لدينا رهينة في الأزرق الشرقي
Stealth.
تسلل
I can't believe it... Have you taken a liking to that kitchen maid?
ما خطبك يا هذا؟ هل أنت معجب بتلك الطاهية الحثالة؟
Don't fight back. Otherwise, there will be blood in the East Blue.
لا تقاوم، وإلا ستراق الدماء في الأزرق الشرقي
Henry...
الإبرة
Needle!
الكهربائية
You should've told me.
كان عليك إخباري
If I knew you were in love with that kitchen maid,
لو أنني علمت بإعجابك بتلك الطاهية الحثالة
I wouldn't have messed up her face.
لما أفسدت ملامح وجهها
But if you have no problem with that swollen face,
لكن إن لم تكن تمانع رؤية وجهها المتورم
I'll appoint her to be your servant right away.
فسأعيّنها كخادمة لك في الحال
Once again, welcome back, Sanji.
...أرحب بعودتك مجددًا يا سانجي
To the Vinsmoke family!
إلى عائلتنا فينسموك
I think it's high time we reestablish the hierarchy here.
ربما حان الوقت لإعادة توكيد تسلسل مراتبنا
You are... a failure.
أنت فاشل
Listen! You children are my greatest scientific achievements!
انصتوا، أنتم أعظم إنجازاتي العلمية
You were born as superhumans through scientific modifications
ولدتم كبشر خارقين بفضل تعديلات علميّة
representing the best that research has to offer!
تمثّل أفضل ما يمكن للأبحاث تقديمه
Without living under the sway of foolish emotions,
جميعكم ستتحررون من قيد المشاعر السخيفة
each of you will eventually lead your own troops
وسيقود كلٌّ منكم جيشه الخاص
and one day rule Germa 66 with the ever-evolving power of science!
وسيقع حكم مملكة جيرما 66 على عاتقكم لتحقيق أعظم الإنجازات باستخدام قوة العلم
I have given you the ability. The rest comes down to discipline!
منحتكم القدرات، وبقي لكم أن تتدربوا
Yes, Father!
حاضر يا أبي
Now, Prince Sanji!
هيا يا سانجي-ساما
Ow, ow, ow...
...مؤلم
Ouch! Ouch! Ouch!
مؤلم، مؤلم، مؤلم
Where's Sanji?
ماذا عن سانجي؟
I don't know.
لا أعلم
Come on. Come on.
هيا، هيا
Come here.
فلتصل إلى هنا
Stop playing with a turtle!
كفّ عن اللعب مع السلحفاة
How dare you!
كيف تجرؤ على فعل هذا؟
Don't talk to me like that!
يا لك من مغرور
Humph! That'll teach ya!
هكذا ستتعلم الدرس
– Prince Sanji! – Prince Niji!
سانجي-ساما - نيجي-ساما -
Stop! Ouch!
توقف، هذا مؤلم
I give up! Niji!
أنا استسلم يا نيجي
Oh, please stop!
أرجوك توقف
Your Highness...
نيجي-ساما
Let go! I still wanna hit him!
دعني، ما زلتُ أريد ضربه
Why is Sanji weaker than the others? He's lagging far behind the others' scores.
لماذا سانجي أضعف من الآخرين؟ فارق النتائج بينهم يزداد اتساعًا
We have the test results.
تلقينا نتائج الاختبار
The Young Masters Ichiji, Niji, and Yonji are making excellent progress.
إيتشيجي-ساما ونيجي-ساما ويونجي-ساما يبلون حسنًا
Their exoskeletons are developing well,
تطورت هياكلهم الخارجية، وصارت قدراتهم مماثلة للجنود الأقوياء من حيث المرونة والقوة
However, Prince Sanji is... It pains me to say...
...ولكن للأسف، إنّ سانجي-ساما
What is it? Say it.
ماذا؟ أخبرني
He must be considered a failure.
يؤسفني القول بأنه تجربة فاشلة
We thought we successfully manipulated the hereditary elements for all four of them.
ظننا أننا قد نجحنا بالفعل في تعديل عناصر الحد السلالي لأربعتهم
But for some reason, Sanji's hereditary elements are no different from when he was born.
ولكن لسبب ما، فإنّ عناصر حده السلالي عادت إلى أصلها
So you mean...
...مما يعني
Prince Sanji is nothing but a human.
سانجي-ساما مجرد بشري طبيعي
Why do you help me?
لماذا تعتنين بي؟
You don't want me to?
أتريد منّي ألّا أفعل ذلك؟
I do!
كلا
Reiju, you're so kind.
أنتِ طيبة يا ريجو
Shut up! Be quiet!
اصمت، وكفّ عن الحديث
You're kind, but why do you laugh at me?
لكن لماذا تسخرين منّي مثلهم؟
What else can I do?! If I try to stop them, they'll bully me too.
ما بيدي حيلة، إن حاولتُ منعهم، سيتنمرون عليّ كذلك
I don't want that!
لا أريد ذلك
Oh, there he is!
ها قد جاء
You can eat that.
يمكنك تناوله
I made it for you.
أعددته لأجلك
Is it good?
أهو لذيذ؟
Sanji! Are you cooking food for rats again?!
سانجي، هل أعددت طعامًا للجرذ مرة أخرى؟
Royalty mustn't serve anyone! How many times do I have to tell you this?!
كم مرة عليّ إخبارك بأنّ الملوك لا يخدمون أحدًا؟
But, I...
...ولكنني
Your mother is dead! Stop chasing her shadow!
والدتك ماتت بالفعل، كفّ عن تقليد أفعال الموتى
Unlike your siblings, you have no talent!
أنت عديم الموهبة على عكس إخوتك
Therefore, you must work 10 times harder... no, 100 times harder than the others!
لذا عليك بذل عشرة أضعاف، بل مئة ضعف جهدهم
You are a piece of my plan to restore Germa to glory!
أنتم جميعًا جزء من خطتي لاستعادة مجد مملكة جيرما
Do not let me down!
فلا تخيب ظني
Never cook again!
إيّاك والطهو مرة أخرى كذلك
Is that how you run, Sanji?!
أهذه طريقة ركضك يا سانجي؟
No progress.
لا تغير
– So he has no potential. – Right.
إذًا فاحتمال تطوره صفر؟ - أجل -
What a waste of life.
يا له من عديم الفائدة
What should we do?
ما العمل؟
An unthinkable shipwreck... I mourn!
لا أصدق أنه لقى حتفه في حادث، كم هذا محزن
I was expecting all five of them to lead Germa into the future together!
توقعت منهم الخمسة أن يغدون محاربين يقودون جيرما
I have lost a promising son!
فقدتُ ابنًا واعدًا
What?! What is this?!
ماذا؟ ما الأمر؟
What's this? I can't take it off! What are you guys doing?!
ما هذه؟ لا يمكنني إزالتها ماذا تفعلون جميعًا؟
Did Sanji really die?
هل مات سانجي حقًّا؟
I don't know. Who really cares about him anyway?
لا أعلم، ولا يهمني أمر ذلك الأحمق
Wait! I don't wanna be in here!
انتظروا، لا أريد البقاء هنا
Let me out!
أخرجوني
Don't leave me behind! I'm scared! I'm gonna die!
لا تدعوني، أنا خائف، سأموت
I want my dad!
أريد أبي
Dad! Help! They're gonna kill me!
أنقذني يا أبي، سيقتلونني
This was His Majesty's decision.
هذا قرار جلالة الملك
What? Dad's decision?
ماذا؟ قرار أبي؟
No way! There must be a mistake!
محال، لا بدّ من وجود خطأ
His Majesty said that he wants to pretend that you were never born.
قال جلالة الملك أنه يرغب بالتظاهر وكأن سانجي-ساما لم يولد قط
What?
ماذا؟
Why...?
لماذا؟
Please let me out, Dad...
أخرجني يا أبي
I'm sorry... I'm sorry that I was born weak!
أعتذر... أعتذر على ولادتي ضعيفًا
Help me... Dad, help me!
أنقذني، أنقذني يا أبي
Dad!
أبي